http://www.gtu.edu/privacy-policy/personal-data-request

Search
Access the latest, most up-to-date COVID-19 resources, policies, and news for faculty, students, and staff of the GTU, including recent updates from the COVID-19 Task Force here>>
Personal Data Request
Your personal data belongs to you.  This website collects minimal identifiable data via cookie and form collection, and within specific webforms requests personal, identifiable information such as email addresses, full names, phone numbers, and more.  This information is used for internal website traffic analysis and marketing information within the GTU and associated centers and schools and is never sold to third parties.
If you would like to request a report of your own personal data collected and stored by this website, or if you would like to request that your stored personal data be removed/anonymized, you may use the form below to submit your request.  Your request will be reviewed by GTU administrative staff and we will follow up as soon as we are able in order to properly verify your identity and complete your request.
Bear in mind that depending on the nature of your request, a small fee may be required to request your full data record.
Type of Request *
Request My Personal Data Records
Delete/Anonymize My Personal Data
Your Name *
Email Address *
Phone Number
Questions or Comments
Submit
GTU and Title IX
Campus Crime and Safety Report (Clery Act)
Campus Closure Policy
GTU Alerts
Discover the Future of Religious ScholarshipAbout the GTU
Give A Gift to the GTUYour gift - no matter what size – supports innovative research and teaching, and helps equip tomorrow’s leaders for a world of diverse religions and cultures.
Give Now
Stay UpdatedSubscribe to our mailing list and you will receive timely updates regarding important and interesting GTU dates, news, events, and other important information.
Sign Up for the Newsletter
ContrastHigh|Normal
Search form
Search
Main Menu
AboutAbout-HomeOur HistoryQuick FactsAcademic CalendarsExecutive TeamBoard of TrusteesGTU LogoStaff DirectoryCampus MapsBerkeley Overview MapDetailed Campus MapJobs at the GTUGTU StoreAccreditation & EffectivenessPolicies & ComplianceAcademic Policies DisclaimerState AuthorizationComment PolicySafety and EmergenciesCrime LogFire Safety Report and Fire LogPrivacy PolicyPersonal Data RequestsSecurity PolicyInfo & DisclosuresGTU Statement on DiversityGTU and Title IXCampus Crime and Safety Report (Clery Act)Campus Closure PolicyGTU AlertsMapsStudentsDirectoryStaff DirectoryFaculty DirectoryFaculty & StaffSchools & CentersOur Schools and CentersMember SchoolsBerkeley School of Theology (BST)Church Divinity School of the Pacific (CDSP)Dominican School of Philosophy and Theology (DSPT)Jesuit School of Theology of Santa Clara University (JST-SCU)Pacific Lutheran Theological Seminary of California Lutheran University (PLTS)Pacific School of Religion (PSR)San Francisco Theological Seminary (SFTS)Starr King School for the Ministry (SKSM)Academic CentersThe Center for Islamic Studies (CIS)About the CISCourses and Degree ProgramsStudents and GraduatesScholarshipsResourcesMadrasa-Midrasha ProgramVisiting ScholarsCIS EventsThe Richard S. Dinner Center for Jewish Studies (CJS)About the CJSCourses and Degree ProgramsCJS Public EventsPeopleScholarshipsResources and Affiliate ProgramsMadrasa-Midrasha ProgramMultimedia GalleryCenter for the Arts & Religion (CARe)Exhibition CatalogsAdvisory CommitteeExhibitionsArt Loan ProgramSupport the Arts: Become a CARe MemberGrants & Writing PrizeUpcoming EventsThe Mira and Ajay Shingal Center for Dharma Studies (CDS)About the CDSCourses and Degree ProgramsPeopleScholarshipsAffiliates and ResourcesCDS EventsSustainability InitiativeThe Center for Theology and Natural Science (CTNS)Barbour Chair and CTNS CoursesCTNS MembershipCTNS PublicationsCTNS Video and EventsRussell Family Research FellowshipTownes Graduate Student FellowshipAffiliatesCenter for Swedenborgian Studies (CSS)Institute of Buddhist Studies (IBS)Newbigin House of StudiesNew College Berkeley (NCB)The Patriarch Athenagoras Orthodox Institute (PAOI)Projects and InitiativesAsia ProjectWomen's Studies in ReligionBlack Church/Africana Religious StudiesInterreligious Education and Pedagogy ProjectLife, Liberty & the Pursuit of PeaceMadrasa-MidrashaSpiritual Care and Ethical Leadership for Our TimesA Meeting of the WatersA Pilgrimage-in-PlaceA Pilgrim’s Perspective on a Spiritual RebootBe the Change: Student Stories of Action and Resilience in the Face of PandemicOn Our InterconnectednessPersevera y Vencerás: An Abuelita’s Words Revisited during a Global PandemicPracticing What We PreachResources for Building Community and ConnectionSpiritual Care, Resilience, and CommunitySpiritual Reintegration in the Wake of COVID-19The 6 things vulnerable immigrants need you to hearThe Conflict and Ethics of We're in this TogetherTransgressive ConversationsTroubled Times: Turning to the ArtsWhy Black Lives MatterSustainability 360Admissions & AidAdmissions-HomeGTU Degree ProgramsRequest Program InformationVirtual Visit for Prospective StudentsApplying to GTUDoctoral ProgramsCommon M.A. ProgramsCertificate ProgramsInternational StudentsFinancial AidPriority DeadlinesPrograms and EligibilityHow to ApplyAnnouncementsImportant Dates and EventsTuition and FeesCARES Act - HEERF ReportAdmissions Videos and WebinarContact our Admissions TeamTransformative ImpactAlumniGTU AlumniRecent Alumni PublicationsAlumni/ae Contact UpdateGTU Alumni of the YearLibraryLibrary Header MenuSearch GRACEYour Library AccountWorkshopsGuides and TutorialsBack to Main GTULibrary Main MenuLibrary HomeAboutAbout the LibraryDirector of Library Services' OfficeHours and DirectionsGive to the LibraryLibrary Staff DirectoryGeneral PoliciesBorrowing PrivilegesServicesHelp & ReferenceGuides and TutorialsTechnologyOrientation OptionsFeedback and CommentsThesis/Dissertation ApprovalLibrary WorkshopsRequesting Course ReservesInterlibrary LoanServices for Alumni & VisitorsContact UsCurbside Pick-upLibrary ReservationsScanning Services for cardholdersCollections & ResourcesElectronic ResourcesTechnical Services and Collection DevelopmentRecent AcquisitionsSuggest a Library PurchaseFaculty PublicationsSpecial CollectionsSpecial Collections DepartmentArchivesManuscript Collections by TitleFeatured CollectionsEdith Stein, St. Teresa Benedicta of the Cross CollectionOral Histories of the Graduate Theological UnionDouglas G. Adams CollectionMargaret Palmer Taylor Collection of Sacred DanceRobert McAfee Brown CollectionAlbert Gleaves Cohen CollectionSanctuary MovementAnne McGrew Bennett Collection, 1959-84The Center for Women and Religion CollectionThe Elsie Thomas Culver CollectionThomas Starr King CollectionThe Radical Religion CollectionPaul W. Yinger CollectionLGBTQ CollectionsPacific Coast Theological Society, 1939 - presentFrankl Collection and LogotherapyNew Religious MovementsNew BooksNews & EventsLibrary News and EventsArt Exhibitions at the GTU LibraryReading of the Sacred TextsRemote Resources for the GTU LibraryAcademicsAcademics-HomeDoctoral ProgramFrequently Asked QuestionsProgram DemographicsApply to the Doctoral ProgramMA ProgramFrequently Asked QuestionsStudent HandbooksApply to the MA ProgramInterreligious Chaplaincy ProgramAbout the ICPAdvisory CouncilApply NowFrequently Asked QuestionsICP CoursesScholarshipsInterreligious Studies Certificate (Online)Certificate ProgramsAsia ProjectAOCFT CertificateAsia Project Recommended CoursesHistory of the Asia ProjectPast ProgramsResourcesWomen's Studies in ReligionAbout the ProgramCertificate RequirementsResourcesBlack Church/Africana Religious StudiesAbout the ProgramCertificate RequirementsColloquium SeriesCertificate Programs and Other Study OptionsDepartments and ConcentrationsSacred Texts and Their InterpretationHebrew Bible/Old TestamentHindu Sacred TextsIslamic Sacred TextsNew TestamentRabbinic LiteratureHistorical and Cultural Studies of ReligionAnthropology of ReligionArt and ReligionBuddhist StudiesChristian SpiritualityComparative ReligionHindu StudiesHistory of ChristianityIslamic StudiesJain StudiesJewish StudiesNew Religious MovementsReligion and LiteratureSociology of ReligionTheology and EthicsAestheticsChristian TheologyComparative EthicsComparative TheologyEthicsHindu TheologyIslamic Philosophy and TheologyPhilosophical TheologyTheology and ScienceReligion and PracticeHomileticsLiturgical StudiesMissiologyPractical TheologyReligious EducationYoga StudiesOur FacultyFaculty DirectoryExperts ListResources for Faculty & StaffAcademic Catalog 2019-2020Course ScheduleCommunity EducationThe Flora Lamson Hewlett LibraryBorsch-Rast Book Prize and LectureshipNomination FormStudent AwardsOnline LearningRegistration Dates 2020-2021Spiritual Care on the Front LinesUC BerkeleyVisiting Scholars at the GTUCalendarContactLife at GTUOverviewBerkeley and the Bay AreaRestaurants and Local EatingHousing in the AreaCal Rec ClubParking and TransportationStudent LoungeNew StudentsCurrent StudentsForms and GuidelinesRegistrars of the GTUConsortial Registration PoliciesClassroom LocationsKey to Course NumbersLibrary/ID cardsCross-Registration Instructions: UCBCross-Registration Instructions: DU, HNU & MillsSRC RegistrationFERPAStudents with DisabilitiesNews & EventsGTU NewsEvent CalendarExhibitionsLibrary GalleryBadè Museum of Biblical ArchaeologyBlackfriars GalleryMagazines & JournalsGTU Voices BlogInsight e-NewsletterDean's NewsletterLectures and AddressesSurjit Singh LecturesDistinguished Faculty LecturesReading of the Sacred TextsBorsch-Rast LectureshipConvocation AddressesMcCoy Memorial LectureOther LecturesRecent Faculty and Alumni PublicationsVideo and Audio ContentVideo - GTU PeopleVideo - LecturesAudio - About GTUAudio - Signature LecturesAudio - In the NewsAudio - Academic PresentationsGivingGiving-HomeDonate NowWays to GiveOnline GiftGifts of CashStock or Wire TransfersMatching GiftsPlanned GivingContact Us
Connect With Us
facebook
twitter
linkedin
youtube
instagram
